THEME SONG: In the not too
distant future, next Sunday AD,
there was a guy named Joel, not
too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic
Institute, just another face
in a red jumpsuit.
He did a good job
cleaning up the place,
but his boss didn't like him,
so they shot him into space.
We'll send him cheesy movies,
the worst that we can find.
La-la-la.
He'll have to sit
and watch them all,
and we'll monitor his mind.
La-la-la.
Now keep in mind,
Joel can't control
where the movies begin or end.
La-la-la.
Because he used
those special parts
to make his robot friends.
Robot roll call-- Cambot!
Pan left.
Gypsy!
Hi, girl.
Tom Servo!
What a cool guy.
Croooow!
He's a wisecracker.
You're wondering how
he eats and breathes,
and other science facts.
La-la-la.
Then repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show,
I should really just relax for
Mystery Science Theater 3000!"
[DOORS CLOSING]
-Hey, everybody.
Welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
My name's Joel Robinson.
This is my friend Tom Servo.
-Yo!
-Hey, have you seen Crow lately?
-Um, I, uh, think he went out.
-You know, you seem
kind of different.
Did you get a
haircut or something?
-Nope, just Tom
Servo-- sleek and slim
with a transparent head.
-Well, I'm looking for Crow,
because he left his little
Billy doll in my room
again, and I'd like to--
CROW (SINGING OFFSCREEN):
Toasted peanuts.
-Ah, there he is.
Hey!
-(SINGING) 50,000
monkeys can't be--
-Good to see you, Crow!
-Oh hey, Tommy.
Top o' the morning to you!
-Morning.
-Uh, Joel, have you seen my
"Utne Reader," by any chance?
-What's going on?
-Uhh, it's Tuesday.
-Paranoid delusions.
-It's treatable, you know?
(OFFSCREEN): Commercial sign!
Commercial sign!
Commercial sign pretty soon!
-Loading Richard
Basehart remark.
Richard Basehart remark
in five, four, three,
two-- Richard Basehart now.
-I get it.
I know what's going on.
-No, no Joel, you don't get it.
You're crazy.
-I think you're insane, Joel.
-(SINGING) Crazy--
-We'll be right back.
-(SINGING) Toys in the attic.
He is crazy!
-Joe.
Joe!
Hoo-hoo.
[THEME MUSIC]
-Well, you see, Joel, we
reversed the mini data
flow of our voice sequencers.
Quite simple, really.
-I wrote the funny jokes.
-Yeah, you guys
are about as funny
as the urinary tract infection.
Oh, W.W. and the Dixie
Dancekings are calling.
-Hello, bubbi.
I don't mean to rub
it in, but we're
entertaining a few celebrities
here in the Deep 13 grotto
room.
-Well, look at all of them.
George Kerby just got here.
Dick Gautier just arrived.
Vikki Carr, just to name a few.
Wow, what a party!
-You know, Joel, our invention
this week is made for men.
-But the ladies like it, too.
[CHUCKLES]
-What is it?
-We can't show you what it is.
But get this.
We're wearing it.
Sh.
-Oh come on, you guys.
You didn't invent anything.
-Well that's what
you'd like to think.
It's comfortable, easy
to wear, glides on easy
and stays in place.
-I shower in mine.
People say I look
more confident,
which results in more sales.
Shouldn't we be, uh, telling
him to do an invention exchange?
-Frank, you're
ruining it for me.
-Today's invention
exchange, sirs,
is based on the
premise the kids love
to read the back
of cereal boxes.
-That's why we've come
up with cereal novels!
-Modern fiction-- it's all part
of this nutritious breakfast!
-You see, right now,
Joel is reading Interview
with a Vampire on the
back of Count Chocula.
Maybe later, he'll eat
some Anne Rice puffs.
I'm just kidding, of course.
-Read Kaboom cereal
with Bret Easton Ellis's
controversial yet
all but forgotten
American Psycho on the back.
-And for the more
adventurous, you
can start your day
eating Lucky Charms
while reading Thomas
Pynchon Gravity's Rainbow.
It's magically obscure!
-Ha-ga-ga-ga--
-What do you think, sirs?
-Joel, this week's
experiment stars
Casey Adams of
Catalina Caper fame.
-Tell him about it, Lawrence.
-You got me.
It's called The
Indestructible Man,
but first, I'm
afraid you're going
to have to sit through another
chapter of Undersea Kingdom.
-Oh, Frank, look.
There's Jerry Van
Dyke with his banjo.
-Wow!
[SCREAMING]
[DOORS CREAKING
AND GRINDING OPEN]
-It's October.
-Das people.
Das credits.
-Park it anywhere, crab.
-Red Rover, red Rover, let
B. Reeves Eason come over.
-Two directors?
-Hey!
-(SINGING TOGETHER) Hey, it's
the undersea kingdom for you
and for me, where the
men are in dresses!
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
-We have to dry our swords out!
-And around the Clubhouse
10, there goes Beetlejuice up
the front, and Krapalm
brings up the rear.
-(SINGING) Ooh-ooh-ooh,
Monte Blue.
-Hey, you kids!
Come in here with
my pillowcases!
-Yeah, we know.
Into the valley of death
right at the 600, we know.
-Did you hear something?
-Hm?
-It's the UPS man!
Lon Cheney, Jr?
Nooo!
-Hmm, the John
Bradford Exchange.
-Come on, guys.
Let's go get greased,
big time. (CHUCKLES)
-Oh, cute.
-(CHANTING) Unga Khan!
Unga Khan, Unga Khan,
mad tyrant of Atlantis.
Unga Khan, Unga Khan.
The tyrant of Atlantis.
-(SINGING) I wanna
rule with you.
-Actually looks like Jimmy
Carl Black, doesn't he?
-It's the bishop!
-[IMITATES_STRINGED_INSTRUMENT]
-What is this, their yearbook?
-Editor, yearbook
two, three, and four.
Burnout, three and four.
-Known for his anthologies,
Professor Norton, that is.
[CHUCKLES] You see, because--
-It's Averell Harriman.
-Diana, a go-getting
newspaper-- oh, in other words,
she fetches.
-I totally didn't vote
for her for homecoming.
-Huh-uh.
-Next slide, please.
Ne-- thank you.
-You may remember him from
the Cracker Jacks box.
They opened him up and
found a prize inside.
-Gee.
-The sailor's favorite.
-President of hat club, three
and four, grandest of all four.
-Uh, sorry, it never starts.
Oh, there we go.
-Let's cut through
the salad bar!
-Gin tanks are attacking!
-Ooh.
Ooh.
-So they weren't killed, gee.
-Shut up, dummy man.
-You two get behind that rock!
Billy and I will lead them home.
-Which rock?
-Run, Crash!
-(IMITATIVE) Run, Crash!
-Two of the strangers
have escaped the Volkites
and are heading for the beach.
-Oh, they're watching
"North by Northwest."
-(IMITATING BACKGROUND
MUSIC) Do-do-do-do, do-do-do,
do-do-do.
-Pick up a ray
gun soon, Captain.
-(SINGING) Western Union.
Do-do-do-do do-do-do-do do-do--
(SINGING RESUMES) Do-do
do-do-do do-do-do-do--
-We must defeat them.
-In this gown?
Hey, it's an old rug beater.
-From "Beauty and the Beast."
-Hold me closer, tiny sailor.
-(SINGING) I feel the earth--
-(IN RHYTHM) Mm.
-(SINGING) Move--
-(SINGING) Under my-- whoa!
-That's dirty!
-Jump through that man pipe.
-Aw, cheap, cheap, really cheap.
-Boo.
-Hey, the interstate, Billy.
Good luck.
-How'd they get off
the cockadoody cliff?
This is wrong!
-Diana!
-Oh, great, water heaters
that install themselves.
I love it.
-I'm riding shotgun.
-You are a shotgun.
He.
-It's the Von Trapps!
-There's a way out!
-(HARSH FALSETTO)
There's a way out!
-If those mechanical men can't
follow through those plains.
-There's Cilla and Pergdus.
-Look!
-Look, it's the quad cities!
Ooh.
-Are you sure this is the
lost continent of Atlantis?
-Billy looks like
William Frawley.
-What a story this
will make for my paper.
Hero reporter
discovers civilization
10,000 feet below the ocean!
-A regular Nina
Totenberg, isn't she?
-I'd like to explore that city.
-So would I.
-Perhaps we'd better get
back on the submarine
before we run into anymore
of these strange creatures.
-Uh, perhaps you should get back
to acting on the stage, Gramps.
-Do they all have to touch
each other when they talk?
-You're a better man
than I, Gunga Din.
-The man who would be queen.
-Look closely, Martos.
Have you ever seen
such people before?
-No.
-Everybody skip!
-But I betcha they're in
league with Unga Khan.
-Unga Khan.
-Is that Matt Dillon?
-Hi!
-Which one of us
is he waving at?
-Follow me!
-Oh, it's Jim Henson's
Birth of a Nation babies.
-Oh.
-(MOCKINGLY) Follow me!
-Look at all those
horses under the sea.
-So how do they get
them under the sea?
-Sea horses?
-D'oh!
Oh!
-Ben Hur.
-Ben Hecht.
-Charles MacArthur.
-Jimmy Smits.
-Ah, here's the stop.
Everybody get transferred.
-[HUMS ALONG WITH
BACKGROUND MUSIC]
-OK, if things get tough,
we'll offer 'em Billy, agreed?
-Cool.
-Agreed.
-Oh, it's like the end of
a high speed chase in LA.
-Ride back to the
Sacred City and report
to Sharad, High
Priest of Atlantis,
that we are returning
with strange prisoners.
-Weird prisoners.
-(SHRILLY) I wanna
ride with Diana!
-Uh, you're a little late
for the posse, fella!
-(SIMULTANEOUSLY)
Da da-da-da-da,
da-da-da, da-da-da-da da.
-The end.
-Oh.
-With Mark Spitz,
Jimmy Smits, and Rossy,
the French wonder horse.
-Open the gate!
-It's Martos.
-Open the gate and make
some summer sausage, quick!
-Too late.
-Ouch.
-Open the back door!
He can't stop!
-Here, wash and wax this.
-Thank you, sir.
Ah, jeez, all I got is a crummy
popcorn ball and some Jujubes.
-Looks like a set The
Monkeys would end up on.
-Confident, dry, and secure.
-Darius approaches the
city with strange captives.
-Strange captives?
-Weird captives.
Kept
-Where are they?
-We believe them to be
agents of Unga Khan.
-Unga Khan.
-That sucks.
-There will be no
peace in Atlantis.
-Can we break your hat open
now and eat the popcorn?
-Power of this evil
usurper, Unga Khan.
-Anderson Windows
and Wall-- Doors.
-Before we could return
and capture the strangers,
the Volkites appeared
and destroyed them
with their atom guns.
-I wanted them alive!
-They are alive.
-Well then everybody's happy.
-Well then, shall we eat?
There's Dutch loaf.
-Sharad's men have captured
them, Your Majesty,
and they're heading
for the Sacred City!
-Enough TV for you two.
Now get outside and play!
-Recapture the
prisoners at any cost.
You
-Hi-keeba.
-Oh! [IMITATES SOUND
OF HEADS BUMPING ROCK]
-Owie!
-Oh, my head.
-My head.
-Oh, watch out in back!
-Ow!
[HUM ALONG WITH
BACKGROUND MUSIC]
-Oh, look.
It's the three horsemen--
no, the four horsemen-- no,
the several horsemen
of the apocalypse.
-Oh, Mother Superior
jumped the gun.
-Nope.
-Whooaaa!
Big hill, everybody!
-Well, what do you know?
[THEME MUSIC]
-Ooh.
-The Dick Clark story on ABC.
-He any relationship
to Dick Cheney?
-I don't think so.
-Oh.
-Marion?
-TVs Marion from Happy Days.
-It sounds like the
soundtrack is drunk.
[EXAGGERATEDLY IMITATES MUSIC]
-Oh, Ted Fleshman, Jr., John
Russell, Jr., Lon Chaney, Jr.,
Sammy Davis, Jr., Junior
Samples, Junior Absorbing, Jr.
-Lots of juniors.
-(TOGETHER) Vy
Russell in flight.
[BUZZES] Afternoon
delight-- aww.
-It's cute, huh?
-Pollexfen, for
your "denfentures".
-Den-then-ten-tures.
-All of justice?
That's kind of a gross
exaggeration, isn't it?
-It's not a court of justice.
It's a court of law.
-Who is Detective Division?
-Hmm.
-I'm Lieutenant Dick Chasen.
-He's eating breakfast.
-This hadn't been
a routine case.
And to find the answer, I've had
to put a lot of little pieces
together.
-It's parents' day at Attica!
--most cases can
be called closed.
It was the day before the
Butcher was to be executed.
-He was visited by his attorney
Paul Lowe in the death-house.
-San Quentin Crisp.
Cute.
-It was at this first
meeting the Butcher Benton
case took its first switch.
-Jimmy Smits.
-One last tip, Butcher.
The evidence against
you is so strong,
the government turned
down your appeal.
-Aww, they still
think your father's
more talented than you are.
-You started rough,
and now you're
still trying to throw me curves.
-Look, I don't blame
you for being edgy,
but get this straight.
I didn't double cross you.
I never worked
harder for a client.
-You mean you never
worked harder for a client
to get him sentenced.
-Oh.
-Oh, that hurt.
-You're a fool, Butcher.
If you hadn't tried to double
cross Squeamy Ellis and Joe
Marcellia, they wouldn't
have turned state's evidence
against you.
-Touche.
-But you had to get greedy.
You wanted to keep the
whole $600,000 for yourself.
-Which one's in jail?
-Hmm.
-Boys got sore, and
I don't blame them.
-It was all your idea.
You planned the whole job.
You hired us.
When you found out
I'd staked the money,
you decided it was
time for me to die.
-Shh, Mom's here.
-You got those two crumbs to
turn state's evidence on me.
You stinking rotten mouthpiece.
-That's Mr. Stinking
Rotten Mouthpiece to you.
-Now look, what's the sense
in not giving me the money?
It's not gonna do you any good.
-Oh yeah.
Yeah.
-It's locked up in a CD.
-I'll have the satisfaction
of knowing that none of you
three crumbs are gonna spend it.
-What about Eva?
-Don't you owe her something?
You tell me where
the money is, I'll
see that she gets your share.
-I've got a different idea.
I'm going to kill you
and Squeamy and Joe.
Then I'll take
care of Eva myself.
-Neat.
-You thick-headed ape,
you're gonna die tomorrow.
-Oh, that's right.
I stand corrected.
-Remember what I said.
I'm gonna getcha.
-Sucker.
-All three of ya.
-Wait, there's only one of me.
-Even for you, Butcher,
that'd be quite a trick.
So long, dead man.
-OK, see you late--
[SPUTTERS] Hey!
-Remember what I said.
I'm gonna kill you.
All three of you.
-The butcher, the baker,
and the candlestick maker.
-The thief, the
cook, the wife, and--
-Whoa-ho, Centerville.
Real great place to
bring your kids up.
-French dips.
-Back in Los Angeles, two
men sat in a bar room,
listening to a newscaster
tell his headline story.
-Oh, I've heard this joke.
-The Butcher's
threatened to kill
Paul Lowe, Squeamy
Ellis, and Joe Marcellia.
-Listerine?
[EXAGGERATED CHEWING SOUNDS]
-For them having turned
state's evidence against him.
-Squeamy Ellis didn't seem
happy over the Butcher's threat.
-(MOCKING) They're not happy
with the Butcher's threat!
-But they had figured, once a
dead man, always a dead man.
-That's smart.
-Like a boy scout.
-Ooh!
-This was one time everyone was
in for a surprise, including
the entire police department.
-Mhm, mhm.
Go on.
Come on.
-Hmm, wonder what Billy's
doing in Family Circus today.
-Wow.
Prime cuts go on sale at noon.
-Building code under fire.
-[GASPS] Oh.
-You see the headlines, Captain?
-Teletype just came
in from San Francisco.
-Here's the receipt
for your paper.
-Set for 5 o'clock
this afternoon.
And like the newspapers
say, he still
refuses to talk about
that stolen money.
-(MUTTERED) Still refuses to
talk about that stolen money.
-Well, I still have hopes
of coming up with something.
-Ooh, he sat on the pen set!
-That's what I
dropped by for, Dick.
Butcher's execution, the
department's marking his case
closed.
That means you'll be reassigned.
-Hmm.
-I spent a whole year
trying to break this case.
As far as I'm concerned,
Butcher's death
is just the beginning.
-Could you reassign me
with Pepper Anderson?
-I can't prove it, but I think
that Paul Lowe was the top man.
And even though I have to keep
working on it while off duty,
I'm going to get Lowe, Squeamy
Ellis, and Joe Marcellia.
-Hmm.
-OK, Lieutenant.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Officially, I've
taken you off the case.
-Touch, touch.
-Unofficially, I wish you luck.
-Hey, you forgot to
pat his head, too.
-Do me a favor.
Keep me posted.
-Will do.
-Wait, isn't this your office?
-Thanks, John.
I headed for Eva Martin.
-But then, who didn't? [PANTS]
-She worked in the
local burlesque house.
I'm a cop, and my job is to
ask questions and get answers.
-All right, talk!
-So I decided I might as
well start again with her.
-Da-dum, da-dum, da-dum.
-And I walked
really, really fast.
Morning!
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Either
those curtains go, or I do.
-Come in.
-Oh, hi.
I saw your sister outside.
You know, the quiet one?
-What do you want?
-I'd like to talk to you.
-Talk?
You're a cop, aren't you?
-That's a good question.
I can't even find a
three-ton armored car,
let alone the $600,000.
I've been on the case a year.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Well you're a crappy cop.
Look, it's 9:00 AM and
I'm dressed like this.
Leave me alone!
-Look, I told you.
I don't know anything
about the money.
I never did.
-Benton's gonna be
dead in a little while.
I thought it might
make a difference.
-I never knew anything
about the money!
-Money, you know?
Medium exchange,
storehouse of value, green.
-I didn't even know Charles was
in the rackets until the trial.
-Now take it easy, kid.
-You're on, Eva!
-Hey, it's Al Jolson.
-What's he doing out there?
-So, uh, can I wear
your clothes now?
-Pff, boy, that burlesque cow
sure puts on a good brunch.
-It's a Jack Ruby planet.
-The Jack Ruby program!
-Oh, damn.
It's my evil twin.
-Well, let's see here.
GWM seeks leatherman for-- oh.
-He's wearing espadrilles.
Oh, even criminals
have to punch in.
What do you know?
-Ha, now I can drink.
-Honey, here's your wrap.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Thanks, Mr. Lithgow.
-Anytime.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
New stuff killed-- oh, hi.
-Oh, mommy.
-It's his mother?
-What a dump.
Who said that?
-Two months ago, Butcher
Benton, without revealing
the whereabouts of the $600,000
stolen in the armored car
hold-up, paid for his
crimes against society
in the gas chamber
at San Quentin.
-Walter Winchell is
hiding behind the curtain.
-There.
Jeez, I hate Howard Stern.
-Come on, baby.
Don't waste tears on Benton.
-I feel so badly about Charles.
If I'd known, maybe I
could've done something.
-How about a drink?
We could both use it.
-An artist can't drink
while she's working.
-Then how about a karab shake?
-Well, I've got blanch
peanuts here, if-- hmm.
-It's from Ed McMahon.
-Well now what's the matter?
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
They spelled my name wrong.
-It's a message from Charles.
He told me to open
it if-- he died.
-[WHIMPERS]
-Finale, Eva.
-All right.
-Jolson again.
-How about a steak
after the show?
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Oh, he always offers me beef.
-Dumb, you stupid
dumb-- the idiot!
What is with me today?
-Hmm.
Well it says here, "Dear Eva,
don't eat too much steak.
Love, Charles."
-Hmm.
-Opening the letter the
Butcher are given Eva,
found the map outlining a
section of the city sewer
system.
-It's his varicose veins.
-Clearly identified
was the spot where
the Butcher had hidden
the stolen payroll.
He replaced it with a $50 bill.
-And a pork chop.
-I guess he figured $50
to gain $600,000 was not
a bad day's work.
-No one will be seated during
the frightening letter-folding
scene.
-Put it in a mutual fund.
[DOORS CLOSING]
-Welcome to the Satellite
of Love's annual Any Excuse
for a Parade parade.
This year, we salute
The Undersea Kingdom.
I'm your host, Alan
Thicke, and my co-host
down on the parade
route is Mary Frann.
-Mary Frann?
You said I could
be Dick Van Patten.
-Oh, sure thing, Dick.
-OK, our first float
is turning the corner
onto Gypsy Rose Lane.
Gypsy, as you know, is
this year's grand marshal.
-Always an honor!
-This float is a tribute
to Ray "Crash" Corrigan.
-And it's a good thing
Crash isn't driving.
-Ho ho, that's right, Dick.
Hey, look, there's little Billy!
-Hurry, Diane.
-That float is sponsored by
the American Dairy Association
and is made entirely of
recycled milk cartons.
-Dairy, you don't
find it underwater,
but it's got water in it.
The ADA inviting you to enjoy
dairy in all its permutations
at least three times a day.
-Here comes the
Florida Institute
of Marine Biology marching
band, playing the popular love
theme from The Undersea Kingdom.
[GARBLED MUSIC]
-And here's a perennial
favorite, the lovable Tom Servo
from TV's Mystery
Science Theater 3,000.
He portrays Dr.
Norton's submarine from?
-The Undersea Kingdom!
-That's right.
-Did you know, Alan?
It took 18 seamstresses working
round the clock three months
to bring the plucky bot to life.
-In his balloon!
-Mhm.
-And Tom is filled with over
15,000 cubic yards of hydrogen.
-I think you mean helium, Dick.
-Following Servo is the American
Pepper Association float.
Hats off to pepper.
-Uh, pepper.
Up your day with pepper!
-The American Pepper
Association invites
you to try pepper
as a side dish.
-You know, pepper was used
in the miniature sequences
in The Undersea Kingdom to
simulate the ocean floor.
-But pepper.
[INHALING RAPIDLY]
-Look out!
[SCREAMS]
-Achoo!
-(DEADPAN) Oh, no.
Servo has burst into flames.
People are running around.
Fire is shooting.
Oh, oh, the humanity.
Uh, people are
running and screaming.
Uh, we've got commercial
sign, and I'm just
gonna step into
this doorway here.
[THEME MUSIC]
-Two hundred miles--
-[COUGHING]
-San Francisco, the case
took another switch.
Which--
-Jimmy Smits.
--turned the next 72 hours into
one long, hideous nightmare.
-My in-laws came to visit.
-[GUFFAWS]
-Biochemist was
making preparations
for a final experiment
which he hoped
would lead the way
to a cure for cancer.
He'd been successful
with laboratory animals.
-Well, who hasn't?
-The last step called
for a human body.
-That's where I came in.
-Bradshaw's assistant
quickly made a deal
with the local mortuary and
returned to the laboratory
with the dead body
of Butcher Benton.
-Then he hired the winner of
the Joe Flynn look-alike contest
to come on down.
-(GERMAN ACCENT) S'all
right under the sheet?
S'all right.
-You made good time.
-Well, I didn't waste any.
-Any trouble?
-McHale?
-No, I just handed the money
over and moved the body
into your station wagon,
and that was that.
-Good.
-(NASALLY VOICE) This is fun.
-Checking him for change.
-He's in good shape.
-Well, I hope so.
-For a dead man.
-We'll get other
blood samples ready,
then we'll run this
one through fast.
-Right.
-But, uh, first
get junior samples.
-Now wheel him into the
machine and then raise him.
-Raise with a good
Midwestern value.
Loyalty, hard work, you know.
-A little late for a CAT scan.
-We will sell no
wine before its time.
-(BABY TALK) Ooh, he's a
hungry little fella, there.
Isn't he a little hungry fella?
-McHale?
-Elvis!
-Ready?
-You mean you're going to
give him 287,000 volts?
-Yes, yes.
-OK, you're the boss.
-We'll check for that
before we start dissecting.
Turn off the lights.
-We need a dramatic effect.
-He just invented
the Lite-Brite!
-Hmm.
-Ribs!
That's what I'm hungry for!
-Mmm.
-Old boy, if you
respond properly
and my theory is sound, you'll
be more famous dead than alive.
-Like most artists.
-Jimmy Smits.
[ELECTRIC BUZZING]
-It's alive!
It's--
-No.
-Oh.
Aw.
-Bond meter.
-Oh.
-(SINGING) GE, we bring
Lon Chaney to life!
-Inspector Henderson
and Captain Binghamton,
working together
for your future!
-I think it needs
the electric light
orchestra to bring
it all together.
-El Dorado, El
Dorado, El Dorado.
-You see, it goes
all the way to 11.
-Oh, gee, get a garbage
bag and a squeegee.
--rotation of the part.
-(SINGING) Old man, liver.
-Mr. Bradshaw, he's
beginning to breathe.
You've brought this
man back to life!
-With Coast!
-The heart muscle
simply responded
to a terrific electrical
shock, that's all.
-Really?
-Yes, but it does prove that
the cells still function.
-So, lunch?
-Dr. Bradshaw--
-Heal the child within!
-He is alive.
-The shock reaction,
it can't last.
-His cells are multiplying
now, if your theory is right.
-If we could keep that
reaction going longer-- but
it's worth a try.
-Get the body out.
-How come I always have
to get the body out?
-Coffee?
-Come on, get up
for school, faker.
Come on, up and at 'em.
Rise and shine.
Come on.
-Oh, jeez, I've seen calf
liver cuter than him.
-Get some adrenaline
from the supply room.
Some anti-nitrite too.
Hurry, hurry!
-100% pure adrenaline.
-(WHISPERED) Point break.
-Oh, boy.
Did I get electrocuted
last night?
[WHEEZING SOUND EFFECT]
-Senor Wences lives!
-[GROANS] What am I smelling?
Did somebody die in
here?-- oh, I did!
-Uh, oh.
Oh, did I-- did I go
home with you last night?
Oh.
-Can I have a glass of water?
I'm really parched.
-[GRUNTS]
-Hey, now.
-Your heart can't
stand the strain.
-[GRUNTS]
-Now you must lie still.
Please, please.
-Look, my back
teeth are floating.
I've got to go to the bathroom.
-He's got a saggy
diaper that leaks.
-Yuck.
-You're right, I
had that coming.
-Uh, you think people
come back from the dead?
You should see this lab
around quitting time.
[GUFFAWING]
-Back to the Butcher.
He tried to talk, but
the electrical voltage
had burned out his vocal cords.
-Thanks for everything, bye now.
-Hadn't destroyed his brain.
He knew who he was.
He knew who he hated.
-I'm in here!
-Hey, use the damn stairs!
-Kill Lowe, Squeamy,
and Joe Marcellia.
-Hey!
Wait-- oh.
-The electrical voltage that Dr.
Bradshaw had given the Butcher
had increased his
cellular structure
to the point where he
was no longer a man.
-But made for a woman.
-Dr. Bradshaw's
experiment had created
a vicious, brutal animal with
an almost inconceivable amount
of strength.
-So he joined the LA
police department.
-Dr. Bradshaw must have believed
the Butcher's regained life
would last for
only a few minutes.
-If refrigerated.
-Therefore, instead
of calling for help,
the doctor decided to
handle his creation alone.
-Now, easy Benton.
Just relax.
-You relax, I'm dead.
--doctor, and I want
to try to help you.
Do you understand me?
You're in my laboratory.
-You're Milton,
my brand new son.
-You were declared dead.
-Hmm.
-I tried it an experiment on you
and brought you back to life,
although I didn't intend that.
-Uh-huh.
-Now, you've had a great shock.
Now, now come and sit down.
Be quiet, now.
Come and sit down.
-C'mere, I'll fix
you a nice Coke.
-Be quiet, he tells him?
-McHale?
Oh.
I can't wait until
I'm in the boat next.
-Careful.
His reactions are violent.
-How do you explain this?
-Ah, his reactions are violent.
-100 times, perhaps thousands.
His strength is unbelievable.
-Hm.
Gum?
-No, it's too late
for the ammo nitrate.
I want to get some
blood samples,
make some tests on him,
find out what's happened.
Now get me a syringe.
-Yes, sir!
-Good, now get me a sarong.
-Hm?
-Relax, the first one's free.
-What the--?
Oh, I get it.
He's indestructible.
-(IN UNISON) Ohhh.
-You bent my needle,
you freaked out maniac!
-Why won't the needle
penetrate the skin?
-The tissue must be nearly
a solid mass of cells.
-How're we gonna get
the blood samples?
-Molting is very glamorous.
-Surgically, perhaps.
-Surgically?
Wait, I want a second opinion.
-Take it easy.
You can't leave here now.
I'm responsible for
your being alive.
[STRANGLING SOUNDS]
-You're not the boss of me.
[CHUCKLES]
-You know, I really cannot
tell which is more fun to kill.
Huh, it's a draw.
-Huh.
Well, done and done.
Killed two birds with one stone.
Sorry, guys.
Uh, say, you know if there's
a breakfast place near-- oh,
that's right.
You're dead.
Sorry, I forgot.
-(SINGING) This will
be the day that I die.
(SPEAKING) I finally understand
the lyrics to that "American
Pie." (RESUMES SINGING)
Drove my Chevy--
[THEME MUSIC]
-Well, he's wandered
into a Mr. Bulky's.
-Oh, let's see here.
Licorice whips, Jujubes,
Slo-Pokes, Lon chaney,
Junior Mints.
[CHUCKLES]
-Uh, hello?
Anybody work here?
Can I get some service, please?
-Towards the end of this
case, Captain Lauder and I
found out the doctor and his
assistant had been murdered.
But I am getting
ahead of my story.
-I'll say.
-The Butcher didn't know
how he had been brought back
from the dead, and
he didn't care.
-Oh, he's under the bleachers.
-All he knew-- he was alive.
-Kinda.
A little.
-And this
monster-made-man started
thinking about Los Angeles.
-"The Eyes of Laura Mars."
Oh, I feel better now.
Say, this whole coming
back from the dead thing
isn't so bad after all!
Huh!
Now I gotta tap a kidney.
Be right back.
-On that night in Los Angeles--
-Taquitos!
-I decided to stop playing
detective for a little while.
-Dude looks like a lady, huh?
-I went to the
burlesque house to ask
Eva to have dinner with me.
-I think I'm going
to like it here.
-After all, the Butcher was
dead, and if I got lucky,
sooner or later I
figured Paul Lowe--
[CREAKING SOUND EFFECTS]
-Would lead me to
the stolen payroll.
In a way, that possibility--
-I want everybody on stage
for the big Whoville number!
-Want some?
-It's not fair to watch
the show from backstage.
-Next time, I'll pay admission.
-[MAKES_RIMSHOT_NOISE]
-I take it by that remark
you like my routine.
-Yeah, you're pretty good.
-For a guy.
-There's something,
like, kind of spooky
about watching Casey
Adams flirt, isn't there?
-Uh-huh.
-It shouldn't be
hard for someone
like you to get a
job in a class spot.
-If you weren't a
detective, I'd be
willing to bet with
a line like that,
your next remark would
be, "How about dinner?"
[MAKES RIMSHOT NOISE]
-Well, not exactly dinner, but a
hamburger might be a good idea.
-Ahh, meat again?
-If you're asking in an official
capacity, I can't say no.
-She's got a limo.
-I'm off duty.
-For the past six months,
all I've ever called you
is Lieutenant Casey.
Do you have a first name?
-Mhm.
Dick.
-That figures.
-Give me 10 minutes for a
quick change, because you just
made yourself a date,
Lieutenant-- I mean, Dick.
-All right.
[PURRS]
-So why'd they go to Expo 67?
-No, that's Brazil 76.
-I see.
-Well, the guy
spares no expense.
-I haven't had hamburger in
the backseat of an automobile
with a guy in a lot of years.
-(IMITATES FEMALE VOICE)
You're a cheap jerk.
-From now on, we'll
do it more often.
-Fine.
I always figured a policeman
wasn't really a human being.
I mean, unless he was
arresting someone or trying
to solve a case, he was unhappy.
-That's nice.
Pass me the jack sauce.
-In fact, everyone on the
force gets fed up occasionally
with the job they do.
-That's why we beat
up Rodney King.
-Maybe we're more
human than anyone else.
-Huh!
-You see so much trouble,
you begin to hate the world.
But as long as the world's
filled with people,
there have to be men
who enforce the laws.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Um, can you take me home now?
-What made you join
the department?
-Now who's making
with the questions?
-[CHUCKLES_SARCASTICALLY]
-No, honest.
I'd love to know.
-Well, it's really
a very short story.
-By Chekhov.
-When I got out of the Air
Corps, I knocked around.
-[SIGHS_LOUDLY]
-Then I went to work
for an oil company.
-That's why I'm so greasy.
-One day, I went back to
college on the GI bill.
Just before graduation--
-[HUMS_IMPATIENTLY]
-I noticed all about the
police department exams.
-[YAWNS_LOUDLY]
-[EXAGGERATED_SNORING_SOUNDS]
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Can
I throw up out the window?
-I have one more question.
Will you give me
a straight answer?
-Try me.
-Am I still part of your
Charles Benton investigation?
-And how.
-I mean, right now.
-I don't think so.
-(MOCKINGLY, IN UNISON)
I don't think so.
-As far as the
department's concerned,
when Benton was executed,
the case was marked closed.
If it's on to me,
that's not good enough.
-[EXAGGERATED_YAWN]
-I don't follow.
-Well, the $60,000
is still missing.
A fast-talking underworld
lawyer like Paul Lowe
is walking around a free man.
-Better?
-Sure, I'm better.
-Someday, no matter
how long it takes,
I'll get him and the money.
Until I do, the Benton case
for me it's not closed.
-Oh, bravo.
-Yaaaay.
[CLAPPING AND WHISTLING]
-Bravo.
-Charles Benton never told
me anything about the money.
-Well, I've been sure
of that for a long time.
-Yeah.
-But how did you
ever get mixed up
with anyone like the Butcher?
-(IMITATES FEMALE VOICE)
Uh, well, I wanted a good,
lean brisket, and--
-It just happened.
I had a roommate who used
to date Benton all the time.
One day, she packed
and left for Chicago.
Benton carried
the torch for her,
and he used my
shoulder to cry on.
-Then he burned down the house.
-Next thing I knew, we were
having dinner together.
And a few weeks
later, I was labeled
by the police as this number
one suspect and Benton's girl.
But it was never like that!
(YAWNING) Uh-huh, good.
-I made only one mistake.
-Excuse me, guys.
-[STRETCHING_SOUNDS]
-You mean--
-It's a real yawn fest.
-Arrested for the robbery,
you had no idea how--
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Huh?
Oh, oh sorry, I just thought
I'd stretch out a little.
-I want to know what you've
got going on over here.
-I was just sort of looking.
-And all we ever talked about
was Mags, my old roommate.
-No, go.
-Last time I saw him, he
tried to get too friendly,
and that's when I told
him he had the wrong girl.
-Then I had him electrocuted.
-Like I said, I already
made my mistake.
-What about the burlesque house?
-Can we go back there?
-Please, please, when is
this scene gonna end, please?
I'm getting really tired and
cranky, and-- I don't know.
-And I won a beauty contest.
-No!
Not her life's story!
-No, please.
Please get rid of it.
Will you please?
-After which?
-Turn it off!
Turn it off!
-Really.
-Come on.
-And then one day,
I read an ad about--
-Hey, have you no
sense of decency?
Could you please end this scene?
-Yeah, jeez.
-And you know something?
It's like any other job.
-Yeah, where you strip.
-If you're looking
for trouble, you
can find it even
in the school room.
-Oh boy, oh boy.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
That's where I hang out.
-Oh boy, oh boy, oh
boy oh boy, oh boy.
-When the screen
test didn't work out,
why didn't you go on home?
-Why don't you go on home
and stop it! [VOICE_BREAKS]
-Joel, it's OK.
It's OK, honey.
It's OK.
It's OK, I'm here.
-I don't know about you,
but I do eight shows a day,
and at this hour, I'm bushed.
-So do I.
-Oh, I see.
The big brush-off, eh?
-Mind if I drive you home?
-No.
-Mighty Casey has struck out!
-And I'll tell you
something else.
-(IN UNISON) Noooo!
-I haven't minded
anything about tonight.
Not even the hamburgers.
-[INSINCERE_CHUCKLING]
-Kill them!
-I kept playing tag with Lowe.
He made four telephone calls.
Three of them
didn't interest me.
But one did.
The one--
-Break, no!
-To Joe Marcellia.
-Go!
Go go go!
OK, go go!
Go, go!
Go!
-For some unknown reason, I
began to get the feeling that--
-Go, go!
Go go go, go!
-This case was finally about
to explode in my favor.
-Hey, I'm walking here.
-[LAUGHING]
-Ah!
-Aunt Bee, after dark.
-Well look at that!
I've been staggering
on two legs,
but he's doing it on four!
-Try that, you flea bag!
-Well look who's calling names.
At least I ain't a squealer!
A stoolie!
-[YELLS]
-It's David Mamet's
annotation of the Lockhorns!
-All right, Harry,
that's enough.
I'll take care of them.
I wanna talk to them.
-OK, Mr. Lowe.
But any future business
you've got with this psycho,
take care of it
upstairs in your office.
He keeps showing around
here, sooner or later,
he's gonna get slugged--
cripple or no cripple.
-Vic Tayback, ladies
and gentlemen.
[CLAPPING AND CHEERING]
-Ew, she's covered
with dead things.
-Yuck.
-Go away.
-Let me get this straight.
So every table has a bottle
of Old Smuggler on it?
-No.
-I need us sharp.
You'll get one,
after I talk to you.
You sober enough to understand?
-[HICCUPS]
-Yeah.
I ran out of dough.
-I was going to make cookies!
-Look, you used to be the
best torchman in town.
-Well, thank you.
-Now I don't think
you could crack
a safe if you knew
the combination.
-No jobs.
-Torchmen crack safes?
-Nobody wants me since I
turned state's on Benton.
That's your doing.
You told me.
-All right, quit crying.
-Baby.
-I've got a job for you.
If you can stay off
that stuff long enough--
-You know I can
if I've got a job.
How much?
What is it?
-Pays five bottles a week.
-Is two grand enough for ya?
-Where?
-Right there where
we pulled the job.
-Say your leg stopped dead.
-Two grand ain't
much, out of $600,000.
-The other expenses.
Besides, that money's
plenty enough.
-Got kind of a Bruce Willis
smirk, there, doesn't he?
-Now do you want it?
Or do I get another?
-I'll do it.
How soon do you want
me to go to work?
-Duh--
-Set it up tomorrow night.
-Let's us go.
-It's like a
criminal temp agency.
-One.
And that's all till
the job's over.
-Or he broke his thumb.
[THEME MUSIC]
-OK, and your hand burns,
sending a single to your brain
to tell you to move your
hand off the electric heater.
-Oh, so in a way, pain is good.
Otherwise, uh, we might
be hurt and not know it,
and die during social studies.
-Exactly.
It's all part of a bigger plan.
Get it, Crow?
-Yeah, I guess.
-OK.
Everybody knows there's no way a
person could be indestructible.
But just for fun, what would you
do if you were indestructible?
-Uhh, I'd, uh, hammer
nails with my skull!
No, no wait!
I'd be a high performance
drill bit, or, uh--
-I'd jump in a stump
grinder to amuse my friends.
-Really?
-Oh, sure!
Better yet, I'd rent 15
acres of wooded farmland
and invite people to hunt
me down-- for a small fee.
-Oh, good one, Tommy.
How about this?
Um, I'd invite college students
to staple announcements
and posters on me,
and let them open
beer bottles with
my eye sockets.
-Oh, then I'd allow myself
to be used as an ashtray!
-Oh yeah?
Well, I'd wear a wool
sweater without a t-shirt.
-Huh.
-It's Peruvian.
Real itchy, scratchy.
-But you get used
to it after a while.
-Well listen, Crow.
Every indestructible
fantasy does not
have to be gruesome or horrible.
-Yes it does.
-Sure.
-Uh, OK.
Well how about this?
I go down to the
corner every day,
and immolate myself
for money, kind of
like a street performer.
-Yeah!
-Yeah, yeah!
Now you're cooking with Crisco!
Crisco.
Hey, I know!
I'd bob for doughnuts
in a deep fryer!
-I've got one.
I'd date Sean Young
and then cheat on her
with Roseanne Barr.
-Oh, that's kid stuff
compared to this.
Now get this.
I'd march right into the
Department of Justice
and take the Warren
Commission file.
-Ooh.
Well, I'd go to Rome and
unveil the conspiracy
between the mob and the Vatican.
-Oh yeah?
Well, I'd wear, uh, white
tennis shoes with black socks,
and just wait for
kids to beat me up.
[ALARM BLARES]
-Oh my god, movie!
-Whoa.
[DOORS CREAK]
-Ah, well.
-Meanwhile, in
giant gila monster.
-I gotta take a big
indestructible wiz.
-Oh, that's tasteless.
-Sorry.
-I may be indestructible,
but I still hurt inside!
-[WEEPING_NOISES]
-I lost my retainer.
-Oh, they were-- they were
thinking Julie, go away.
-(SINGING) Because
I'm the wanderer,
they call me the wanderer.
-The Butcher was walking
slowly toward Los Angeles.
-The killer awoke before dawn.
-He traveled
through wooded hills
to prevent being seen by anyone.
Finally, he came
to a quiet road.
He stopped to get his bearings.
-Uh, whose woods these?
I think no.
-He saw something else.
-Jessica Rabbit!
-For the Butcher,
that rang a bell.
-I get it, I get it,
I get it, I get it.
I do.
-With a car, he knew
by the next afternoon
he'd be in Los Angeles
in plenty of time
to catch up with the three men
who had double-crossed him.
-Say, if I had a car, I could
be in Los Angeles in time
to catch up to the three
men who double-crossed me!
-Sooo, uhh, live
around here much?
-Well, see, you're
a real gentleman
to be helping
strangers in distress.
I hope you don't mind me
using the babe here as bait.
Quite a dish, isn't she?
-Hey!
-But that's what
she gets paid for--
-I can't believe this.
-Babe, that is.
Yes sir, she's a real
shaker of my outfit.
Carnival man, myself.
Just call me Carny.
-Makes me sick.
-Art Carney.
-Yeah.
Well, friend, we're in a
little bit difficulty, here.
Got a flat tire, brand new
car, no tools in the back.
Why, some of these dealers--
-He does go on.
--make my my carnival business
look like babes in the woods.
-Indestructible jerk.
-I lo-- love this car.
-Huh.
-The time pedal, in color.
Duh-- Tony, where are you?
-My back!
-Say, who you with, friend?
And let it down!
Let it down.
-I'm with AAA.
-No matter who you're
with, friend-- believe me,
I can do better for both of us.
I'll make a fortune
for the both of us.
-Oops.
-The silent scream.
-Uh, I'll write up
the contract, then.
-Be careful, there's
a three on the tree,
and don't ride the clutch!
-Lie detector by Mattel.
-An hour later, the San
Francisco police department
sent out an APB.
-Let me see.
-Big typewriters
were brought in,
and people were fed into them.
-Squads were sent to various
parts of the countryside.
-Scrods?
-(SINGING IN HARMONY)
Car 54, where are you?
-Oh, there it is.
-Higway patrol, starring
Broderick Crawford.
-Be on the lookout
for doughnuts.
-Oh, come on, Joel.
-APB for doughnuts.
-That's really lame.
No more of these doughnut jokes.
-(GIGGLES)
-Oh, pardon me, Tom "I've Got
To Take An Indestructible Wiz"
Servo.
-(THREATENTING) Why, I oughta--
-So, the sirens of Titan, huh?
-Kurt Vonnegut.
-Oh, it's The Cannonball Run!
-[CACKLES]
-Roadblocks were thrown up to
catch the cold-blooded killer
the hysterical
girl had described.
-Excuse me, sir.
You a killer?
-The one the hysterical
girl described?
-And each of their
stories was the same.
So far, none of them had spotted
the car the killer was driving.
-Sam Snead!
-Orders were given
to shoot to kill.
-Shoot it down, shoot to kill.
-They realized they were
dealing with a maniac.
-Who was dancing like
he's never danced before.
-Whoa.
-Yeah, I'd like to
see your license, sir.
-Oh.
-Take it out of
the wallet, please.
Sir?
-Huh.
-[SCREAMS]
-Huh, mind if I play
through? [CHUCKLES]
-Sam Snead!
-Huh, well, I suppose
they do those things.
-Money.
Revenge.
Money.
[HONKS]
-Honk if you're indestructible.
-If you were indestructible,
you'd be home by now.
-Oh, Wall Drug, 2,000 miles.
-Gee, if I could only read.
(GUFFAWS)
-Yeah, he's indestructible,
but he needs a light wrap,
you know?
-Right, well the boy gets cold.
-More for looks.
-Hall of Justice.
Over 1,000,000 served.
-[IMITATES_BACKGROUND_MUSIC]
-Captain J. I. Estee Lauder.
-I trust this information will
answer all of your questions.
If I can be of any further
service, let me know.
-Your total is $4.35.
Please pull ahead.
-Another all-points
from CHB, Captain.
-Eh, we got this
bill from Winchell's.
Uh, it's in the six digits,
so you have to sign off.
-Wait, who's ordering
the specialty doughnuts?
Hold it a second.
I--
-Hit him.
-Words sound like they come
from a bunch of loonies.
-Well, that's that
Barney Miller.
-There it is.
-Sergeant.
-Yeah.
-I want Lieutenant
Chasen to look these over
as soon as he comes in.
-All right, Captain.
-It's some poetry
I've been working on.
-The next morning,
I read the stories
of the brutal murder
of two police officers.
-Really picked me up.
-I also read the
witness's statement
about the bullets having
no effect upon the killer.
-Sunny and 84 today.
New petitions against tax.
-I felt sorry for
the witness, and I
thought about how easily
a person's mind can become
confused when suddenly they
receive a brutal shock.
-Then I went to lunch.
-I couldn't believe a
man existed who could not
be stopped by a slug from a .45.
-(SINGING) Aruba, Jamaica--
-Good morning, Captain.
-Oh excuse me.
-You and the rest of the force
are going on 24 hour duty.
-All right, yeah-- oh.
-Headlines?
-This guy that's
running amok up north.
-Yeah, and he's
running amok, too.
-Last report, he's killed
two police officers.
Made the getaway in a
green Coop heading south.
-When he gets up to four police
officers, we'll do something.
-I've got a hunch this
killer's gonna be our baby.
-I noticed you knitted
a little blue holster.
-Yeah.
-Better get started, Lieutenant.
-OK.
Now I gotta stop at
Bargain Clown first.
-Any new leads on
that hold-up money?
-I think the girl can
probably be counted out.
If any of the others are wise,
they're keep mighty quiet.
-Let it ride for now.
The whole force is
going to be on the spot
until we catch this killer.
-They're doing "Camelot"
across the lot.
-[HUMMING]
-Newspaper'll have a field day.
-Hey, shut up over there!
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
-Mm, Grandma.
-Hey, who says oldsters
can't stay active?
-Gray lady down.
-All hands on deck.
-[WOLF_WHISTLES]
-We were wrong about two things.
The killer was
already in our city,
and we didn't know he
was Butcher Benton.
He headed straight
for Eva Martin.
He went to her dressing
room to get back
the map he had left in
the envelope with her.
He wanted first to
check his money,
then catch up with
Lowe and the others.
-And if anybody's
interested, he's
gotta pick up his shirts
at the cleaners later, too.
-Hey, I'm voting in here.
-Oh.
-(SPUTTERING) But
I was, and then,
you were dead with the-- ohh.
-Honey, I'm home.
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Oh, well.
-It can't be.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE):
I know I'm a little under--
over-- uh, I don't know
how I'm dressed, but--
-You do look like him.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) And
you do smell like him, too.
-Carl Balentine?
-McHale.
-It is you.
-Why didn't somebody tell me?
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
No, but you're not now.
I need to be up right now.
-Those look like bullet holes.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Well,
I can patch that up easily.
I have a needle and thread.
-There's not even a mark.
-Hm.
-Darling, out of the way.
-Uh, I think
scissors beats hand.
-Yeah.
-See there?
Look, get it?
No ow.
OK?
-Hmm.
Now watch this.
No paper cuts!
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) But
you speak in riddles, Sahib.
-I opened it like you told
me, and found the $50.
-I had $51!
What happened to my dollar?
-I didn't know why he left it.
Paul didn't know
why, and he was here!
-Oh, focus!
-Whoa.
-Hey!
-Lay's potato chips.
No one could eat just one.
-What am I doing?
-Don't-- don't get crazy.
-[GROWLS]
-The name of Paul
triggered his hate.
-The name Gary made him happy!
-Go figure.
-Started for Squeamy Ellis
and Joe Marcellia's place.
Because he knew with
them out of the way--
-Hey, look.
There's a Spike
Lee play showing.
-Paul Lowe couldn't
open the strong box
where the money was hidden.
-Hey, I think that's
a J. Crew barn jacket.
-Ooh, I think you're right.
-Leave Paul Lowe for last.
-Ooh.
(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Hello, everybody.
I'm Gypsy. (SINGING)
Let me entertain you.
-See, school days.
-Oh!
-Oh, OK.
-Travis Bickle.
Taxi driver.
-Well, maybe I could just
take out a loan for $600,000.
-I gave him money for
taquitos, and now he's gone!
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Um,
did you see an indestructible
man walk past here?
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Oh, I'll go cover up, huh?
Thank you, shoe shine,
you're humble and lovable.
-Yes'm.
-Weird.
-Where the-- oh say!
-Oh, that's my change leg.
-Gentlemen prefer change.
-Mhmm.
-Prefer legs.
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Yes, um,
I'd like to order that
diamond-studded necklace
and the gold--
-Eva, can I borrow
your eyebrow pencil?
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Um, sure.
But I've got pink eye.
-Operator, get me
police headquarters.
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Why should I?
What's in it for me?
-And the operator
says $0.40 more.
-When do you expect him?
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE)
Well, does he have voice mail?
-Tell him Charles
Benton is alive.
And-- and even bullets
can't stop him.
I'm not crazy!
-You're crazy.
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Oh, is this tuna?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have the wrong number.
-A friend of Charles.
He'll know.
-Eh?
Well, blow it off
your heart, sister.
I've got the-- wait a minute--
-Eva telephoned Squeamy Ellis.
She tried to tell him
the Butcher was alive.
-Don Rickles.
-And on his way
over to kill him.
-What do you know?
-Squeamy didn't believe
her, and in a way,
you couldn't blame him.
Who in their right
mind would believe
a man had returned
from the dead?
-Only millions of Christians.
-What Squeamy
actually believed was
that the Butcher,
before his execution,
had hired a killer to
carry out his threat.
-Aw, just like F/X. And F/X2.
-Oh, good, a Dr.
Pepper lip smacker.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Hmm.
Honey, how do I get Nathan
Detroit to marry me?
-What?
-You don't look so good to me.
-Well, you don't
look so hot yourself.
-All right.
Say Eva, I could take over
the matinee trick for ya.
-Oh, you'd like
that, wouldn't you.
-It's easy!
Look, Eva, I can do
it. [BEGINS SINGING]
-No, no, please!
I exude you!
-Francine, I just
thought of something.
-Yeah?
-Eva agreed to let
Francine do the show.
-Whoa!
What happened to her voice?
-I dunno.
-She hoped she'd be able to
interrupt the Butcher before he
arrived at Squeamy's hotel.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Gee,
I hope I'll be able to interrupt
the Butcher before--
-At least be able to warn
him to stay out of sight.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) I'll
at least be able to warn him
to stay out of sight.
-You wanted me, Captain?
-For years.
-Yeah, I just had a run-down
on those fingerprints
for the stolen car up north.
We got nothing on the
driver who was killed
or the woman with him.
-Yeah, now Camelot's
opening across the street.
-Take a good look at these.
-Oh, let's see.
Oh, I didn't know
you were an artist!
You drew Binky.
-Something funny about these.
-Yeah, you got the
nose all wrong.
-The boys in the lab can't
figure it out, either.
Those are the killer's.
They were found on
the steering wheel.
Look like they've been
stamped in with a steel die.
-A steel die?
-Oh, and, uh, I
drew this pirate.
-These are Butcher Benton's.
-What?
-They look the same to me.
How do the lab
boys explain that?
-(SINGING) Lab
boys are delicious!
-Their best guess
is a twin brother.
An identical twin could
have the same pattern
of burrows only
slight variation.
-Like Schwarzenegger and DeVito?
-Ever hear of the Butcher
having a twin brother?
-Huh, does that go to the
tune of Alexander's Ragtime
Band? [CHUCKLES]
-Even if it did, it wouldn't
explain these freak prints.
-No, Fresh Prince.
-You didn't pick up your
message, Lieutenant.
Some wacky dame called you.
-(FALSETTO) Joanne Whalley.
-She says Charles
Benton is alive,
and bullets won't stop him.
-Ha, me and the boys got a big
laugh out of that one, sir.
-If we buy the twin theory--
-Who was she?
Where'd she see him?
-Well, she wouldn't
leave her name.
Sounded kinda hysterical to me.
Said she was a friend
of the Butcher's.
-Eva Martin.
-Get over to the follies and
see what that girl knows.
-And, uh, get me a bag of
taquitos while you're there.
-Some guys have all the luck.
-Some guys have all the pain.
-I never do an assignment
to the Follies.
-Eh, shut up and get
me a cup of coffee.
-And a prune danish?
-No, Joel.
-Don't forget to
play Jack Ruby's.
[HUMMING THE "ODD COUPLE" THEME]
-He didn't seem to be
in any particular hurry.
-No.
-Actually, he seemed
like any normal person.
-Yeah, except maybe for the
fact that he was indestructible!
-Hey, watch where you're going!
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
-Ah!
-Excuse me!
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
-(SINGING) Saute and simmer,
the flavor can't be beat.
Do-do do.
-Scanned the hotel
building and then
noticed the only exit
from Squeamy's apartment--
and how he escaped.
-Hey, Lon, could you
pretend you've got the DTs?
[CHUCKLES] Poor sucker.
[SHRILL MUSIC]
-Hey, who's playing a theremin?
-Hope I'm not coming
at a bad time.
-[SNICKERS] (SCOTTISH ACCENT)
Somewhere in the world,
the sun's over the yardarm.
Oh, sweet boys tempt me
to the elven king, oh--
-He's not very
good at spit takes.
-Eh? (DRUNKENLY) Fine,
I'll get to work now.
I have some things to do.
I should head down
this fire escape.
-Ruth Buzzi?
-No, Oscar Wilde.
-Oh.
-It's got little
bird-like movements.
Chirpy.
-(STUPIDLY) Doy, Romeo?
Duhh, Romeo, wherefore
art duhh Romeo.
-(SINGING) Looks like a
pump, feels like a sneaker.
Huh?
-This is just like Vertigo!
-Kind of.
-Sorta.
-Yeah, this has all the
suspense of a Brian De Palma
version of a Hitchcock movie.
-Oh, here comes Brick.
-A-brac.
-Hey look, John D.
Rockefeller saves a Kmart.
-Not surprised.
-Out of the way, Carl Sandburg.
Got a stupid--
-Ah, it says wait outside!
-It says wait outside.
Oh, gee.
-(SINGING) I was
limping in Memphis.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) Oohh,
Jane, stop this crazy thing!
[GIGGLES] (SINGING) Clang,
clang, clang went the trolley.
-Plod, plod plod, went the plot.
-[CHUCKLES]
-Hmm, there are so many
places of historical interest
on this route.
-Looks like she's dressed
for her shift at Hardee's.
[HOCKING A LOOGEY]
-Hair, by Shemp Howard.
-Hey look, the jodes are
waiting for the street car.
-Oh.
-Towels, furnished by La Towel.
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Um, hi.
Anybody want comps for tonight?
-(SINGING IN GRAVELLY VOICE)
Oh, up on Cripple Creek,
she sends me.
If I spring-- oh!
-Whoa!
Foot, don't fail
me now! [CHUCKLES]
-Hey, look, you paid
for the cookies.
I'm just trying to find
a way to drop them off.
-Acme Collection Agency--
uh, sir, uh, you're
three months behind.
-Give me that.
-[SIREN_WAILS]
-Ooh.
-Oh no, he just
killed Rescusci Annie!
-Stop, or the foley
artist will shoot!
-(IMITATING FEMALE
VOICE) Father Karras!
-(SINISTER WHISPER) Regan!
[THEME MUSIC]
-The Butcher was
figuring his next step.
And as he looked
at the dead cop,
he thought about Paul Lowe,
the next man on his list.
-(DRUNKENLY) I
could've been happy.
Ann Francis came here.
-Last night, when I told him
I didn't want him around here
no more.
-Gimme a shot.
-Has there been a
Henry Chinaski in here?
-Ray Walston and Ruth
Warrick in "Barfly."
-Well.
-So, uh, scotch?
-Look, I need help.
I'm Red Buttons.
-I just found out that Benson's
hired a killer to get me.
He's after Joe, too.
-Well then drink up and get out.
I don't want no
trouble around place.
-You're a real pal.
-Drink up and get out, I said.
-Packed with minerals,
Booze really satisfies.
-Ooh, could I lick the glass?
-Oh, Wendy.
-A directory for the alley.
-Well, each bum has
a listing, there.
-Look at all the neat shops.
(IMITATING SEDUCTIVE FEMALE
VOICE) Going up, Mr. Chaney?
-Uh, next up, the food court--
Taco John's, One Potato, Two,
Great American Hotdog
Experience, Puffy's.
-Puffy's?
-Well, I may be indestructible,
but I'm ruled by my tummy.
[CHUCKLES] It says lunchtime.
-Hey, could you imagine
a big indestructible snag
off this thing?
-Oh, yuck.
-It'd kill somebody.
-Snicker-snag Triple.
-Hey!
That's ocupado, pal!
-Hey, look he's in
the cleaver den.
-Oh.
-Excuse me.
Just adding a few
loose ends, here.
-Look, he's casting
Richard Nixon's shadow.
-Oh, my goodness.
-[GUFFAWS] (STUPIDLY) Just
gonna steal a few Post-it notes.
Yep.
-(MUFFLED) If you'd
like to make a call--
-He's really very thorough.
-Now I'm going to rearrange his
filing system. [LAUGHS EVILLY]
-Looks like he's wearing a
catcher's mitt around his neck.
-Say.
-We'll be back after
these messages.
-Needs a shave.
-(NEW JERSEY ACCENT)
Jeez, my appendix burst.
-It's Tom Landy.
-Squeamy, is that you?
-[LAUGHS_STUPIDLY] I have a
sweet tooth-- for revenge.
-Kind of an enigmatic smile.
-Hello?
-Watch me rock.
-Smooth operator-- huh!
-I mind very much if you smoke.
[GUNFIRE]
-Missed me, missed me,
now you gotta kiss me.
-Hey, didn't you see the
first part of this movie?
-Got him.
-[SCREAMS]
-Scream all you want,
but take all you scream.
-[CONTINUES_SCREAMING]
-Linda Lavin?
-[WOMAN_SCREAMS]
-Plop.
-Yep, he didn't come
out of his tuck in time.
-Ah, that's nice.
I'm tired now, but it's
a good kind of tired.
Ah.
-Sara, get me my pilot.
-Operator?
Get me the police!
(FRANTICALLY) Police!
Yes!
-Did she say please or police?
-C'mon, boxcars,
baby needs a new pair
of indestructible shoes.
-What are they waiting
for, a putty knife?
-It kinda looks like rice.
-What's happened?
-Guy named Squeamy got
thrown from the fifth floor.
-Now they call him Squishy.
-Customer of mine.
-Tuh!
-You mean Squeamy Ellis?
-Yeah, that's him.
-How many Squeamies do you know?
-Just Squeamy?
No-- No one else was killed.
-Ain't one enough?
-Wow, everybody's so touchy
at the scene of a death.
-Hulk, you pull the
car over right now.
-I tell you, the bullets
never even phased him.
-Ah, the whole cast is there.
-Wow.
-God help us if the
papers get a hold of this.
-(IRISH ACCENT) All right,
gather around, everybody.
Lots to see.
Show's just starting.
-We're gonna stake out
on Joe Marcellia's.
-John Huston.
-No.
-Lauder, I'm going
to call San Quentin.
Suppose Benton is alive.
-Every available man's
been put on the case now.
Yes, sir.
All right.
All right!
Anything new?
-Well, remember when I got
ahead of myself a while back?
Well, we're at that scene now.
-San Francisco police
located his laboratory
in the basement of an electrical
power receiving station.
-Bradshaw, what's he know?
-He's dead.
And another man
too, his assistant.
The lab is a shambles.
-So's my heart.
-Now we're getting some
action from San Francisco.
Benton's body never
arrived at the mortuary
where it was supposed to go.
An attendant there
finally broke down--
-That's not a very good poem.
Meter's all wrong.
-By handing the body over to a
man he was unable to identify.
The man was driving
a station wagon.
-Oh my god, that's a symbol
of American suburban life!
-The commissioner's are on his,
and the mayor's are on theirs.
Now am I supposed to tell them
that our killer is a dead man?
-They found a notebook
in Bradshaw's lab.
-It said, [SCREAM].
-With a professor
Dwiggins at Caltech.
I hope to hear
from Dwiggins soon.
-Captain, report
from the Valley,
on the hysterical woman.
Reports the presence
of the killer.
-Oh, that was me.
Excuse me.
-Let's go.
-(SINGING) There's a
monster in the valley,
and he's prowling in the alley!
-Hey, check this out, Vern.
When I let go of the steering
wheel, it pulls to the left.
Isn't that something?
-We were just
looking for agates.
-It's Ma Barker's killer brood.
-OK, blow hard.
There you go.
-Now, you and your boyfriend
had a little fight,
and he got out of the
car to take a walk.
-Uh-huh.
-You noticed that he
walked down towards the sun
fair in the direction where
you've seen those lights.
-Uh-huh.
-Before.
-What happened then, Miss?
Please try to tell us.
-Go! [MAKES TICKING SOUND]
-Well, I just sat there,
a few minutes, I guess.
I was pretty mad.
-(IMITATING FEMALE VOICE) I
was fluffing in my car, OK?
-There was a loud
crash, like heavy metal.
-She's only a bust.
-From down here.
I got out of the car
to get a better look.
I heard Jimmy cry out something.
-You said Jimmy Smits?
-Then, down here--
-I wish you'd blink.
-A patch of lights.
-It's like blank.
-That's incredible.
-Really spooky.
-Blink, hello!
Blink!
-Blink!
-Bliiink!
-Like a zombie, blink!
-A big man lifted Jimmy up--
-Please!
-Over his head like--
-She's stuck in
Marsha Mason mode!
-Like he didn't weigh a thing.
-Jimmy screamed.
Just once.
-Go!
-Blink.
-Please, blink!
-What's she looking at?
-I heard it snap!
-It sounded like celery!
-Then I-- I started running
till I found the tide.
They let me use
the phone. [SOBS]
-But--I didn't have friends
and family! [MOCK_CRIES]
-Thank you, Miss.
-[CONTINUES_SOBBING]
-Can I have my tie back?
-O'Malley, see that the young
lady gets home all right.
-Does it have to be her home?
I'm kidding, of course.
-Paul Lowe, while
driving to his office,
heard a radio commentator report
the murder of Joe Marcellia.
And what shocked him most--
-(SINGING) I want to
know what love is.
-Was when the broadcast
identified the killer
as possibly being the Butcher.
Lowe headed straight for
Eva Martin at the burlesque.
-But who doesn't?
-Oh-ho-ho.
-Oh!
You gave me a start, Mr. Lowe.
-Is this where a corsage goes?
-Well, I'm taking her place.
I'm gonna wear her costume.
What's it to you?
-I asked you, where's Eva?
-Hey, don't get physical.
-Let me hear your body talk.
-Then watch the tone
of voice, buster.
I told you, little
Eva isn't here.
-I can see that for myself.
Where is she?
-[GIGGLES]
-Hmm, looks like she's
wearing Fruit of the Loins.
-Oh.
-Oohh.
-That's where she is.
-Yes, sir.
-No sir, Captain Lauder's
still with the mayor.
-No, I'll get out of
your officer, sir.
As soon as poss-- yes,
I'm putting the cigarette
out now, sir.
Yeah.
-Yes sir, we-- we
know he's dangerous.
Every angle.
-He's the other end of
a Bob Newhart routine.
-Yes sir, I-- I'll tell him.
-We'll have to swing by the
7-Eleven and pick him up.
-Well, Mr. Wiggins.
-Huh.
-What the heel are you doing?
-Here, ma'am, I'll just
wear my cop shoes home.
-Thanks.
-(IMITATES FEMALE
VOICE) How come
there's powdered sugar in them?
-Hey, cut with the
doughnut remarks.
-Ah, jokes.
[DOORS CLOSING]
-OK, Cambot, bring it in.
I wanna try that Lon
Cheney eye thing.
Bring it in closer.
More.
Closer.
Come on.
Come on, closer.
Yeah, that's good.
OK.
-(SINGING OFFSCREEN) If I can't
have you, I don't want nobody--
whoa!
-Joel, what are you doing?
-I'm doing an experiment.
-Oh, I thought somebody had
replaced the monitor with
a Jack-o'-lantern.
[LAUGHTER]
-No.
-Oh, bite me.
It's for-- ow!
-Well, you said bite me.
-Oh, come on.
-Oh, good one!
Hey Joel, can we play?
Can we--
-No, ah, ow, ouch!
-Can we get in the shot too?
-Hey, does this bug you?
-No, that hurts, stop it!
-Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
-Joel, better come
down her quick!
Gypsy fell down an airlock,
and her headlight's dilating.
It might be bad!
-Hey, I don't think
I think that's even
funny, not even to joke about.
-Hey Joel, uh, the
men are calling.
They're pretty teed off.
-They really are.
-No, they're not.
-Yep, yep.
-Oh, come on.
[SLURPING SOUNDS]
-Hey, ah, somebody's licking me!
Stop that!
-Nom nom nom nom nom.
-OK, OK, that's it.
Come on.
Back it up, Cambot.
All right, that's it.
-What?
-No, every time I get
something going that's fun,
in run the Batinskis and
stick their little metal nose
in everything.
Well, it's fine.
You guys play.
[INDIGNANT NOISES]
-Go ahead.
You're the kings of everything.
Go ahead.
Enjoy.
-Little lady comes
in here and starts
throwing her butt around,
what was I supposed to do?
-All right, forget
I said anything!
-Maybe I will!
-Well, that's pretty good!
-But don't tell me you
weren't looking at it!
-Well, it's not half bad!
-She's giving it
right back to you!
-What have I wrought.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
-We'll be right back.
-Fine, but it's not
half-bad, is it?
-No, that's pretty good!
-(GRAVELLY) Chili peppers
burn my gut. [GROWLS].
[THEME MUSIC]
-When Lowe came to--
-That's what I'm asking.
-That's pretty good!
-Yeah, hamburgers.
Why can't we ever
have hamburgers?
-Squeamy Ellis
and Joe Marcellia.
-Go on.
-I like your peppermint tie.
-When he slugged
the sergeant, he
knew we'd book him right away.
-Uh-huh.
-Oh, this Lowe's a
pretty cute character.
But we can play the same game.
-You mean we'll
threaten to release him.
-Well, not exactly.
-We'll tease him.
-If you tell him you
realize that he was excited,
that throwing the
punch was accidental.
Tell him we're not
going to make a charge,
that he's completely released.
-Lieutenant, you know
we can't do that.
Lowe made his first mistake
when he hit Sergeant.
That'll get him a year.
As far as the department's
concerned, at least
it's a small victory.
-Now go away.
-If my hunch is right, Lowe
won't want to be on the streets
with the Butcher
looking for him.
He may talk, talk a lot--
-Hmm.
-Enough maybe for us to
get rid of him permanently.
Even lead us to the Butcher.
-Hmm.
-Mm, psychology, eh?
-If he's frightened
enough, that might work.
But if it doesn't--
-We're screwed,
blue, and tattooed.
-Oh!
-I want him out of my way
so bad I can taste it!
But not bad enough to be
responsible for getting him
killed.
-The good thing
about that, Captain,
is the fact that we know
it, but Lowe doesn't.
-Can't resist it when
you put it like that.
-Let's give it a try.
-All right, Lowe.
-All right, Otis, come on out.
-Son, we need you for
another real talky scene.
-I think you'll find
everything in there.
-(FRENCH ACCENT) I think you'll
find your papers in order.
-You're free to go, Mr. Lowe.
-Wow, a leather wallet!
And I was only here for an hour.
-Who do you think
you're kidding?
-You arrested me for
assaulting an officer.
-Ha, I remember you.
-Well, I plead guilty.
-With luck, I might get
off with six months?
-Wallet?
-For a lawyer, you're forgetting
a very important point.
-I care the world for you.
-No charges made,
there's no trial.
It was a tough day for everyone.
We figured your
nerves were on edge,
and when you threw
the punch, you
didn't know what you were doing.
-Yeah.
-I've squared everything
with the sergeant.
It's all over.
All forgotten.
-Kiss, kiss.
You're a good man.
-Why'd you bring a stenographer?
-Simply because I wanted a
record of our conversation
at the time of your release.
-Check out the narcoleptic.
-Buddy?
-OK, Lowe--
-Let's go.
-Now wait a minute.
-He's a sleeping policeman.
-Once out on those streets,
and I'm a dead man.
-If you let me go, you'll
be responsible for murder.
-Oh, come off it, Lowe.
You're imagining things.
-You know the Butcher
threatened to kill me!
-Buddy!
-You set me free, he'll do it.
-Well, that's just a
risk we'll have to take.
-Bob?
You getting any of this down?
Bob!
-Bill!
-You'll be OK.
-Look, Captain, I'll
make a deal with you.
-You end the movie
right now, I'll talk.
-You keep me here, and I'll tell
you how to recover the money.
Maybe even catch the Butcher.
-No deals, Lowe.
-You'd probably tell us
anything just to stall for time.
-Am I that transparent?
-Come on, let's get out of here.
-No wait a minute!
-OK, now.
-All right.
I'll tell you the truth.
Start taking this down.
-You know, I really
am a cop, now.
This is great!
-I--
-OK, get this.
In a hole, in the ground,
there lived a hobbit.
-Squeamy Ellis,
and Joe Marcellia
pull off the
armored car hold-up.
-Can't I just make it up
later, like we always do?
-And then Lowe continued
with his confession.
He told them--
-Seen it.
[SIREN WAILS]
-About finding the map.
He showed us the exact
location of where
the Butcher had hidden
the stolen payroll.
And he gave us a most
important answer.
-The Beatles.
-The explanation as
to how the Butcher
was able to elude detection.
-[HUMMING_TOGETHER]
-He's got a one-bedroom
walk-down with a skylight.
-Oh, nice night.
-Welcome Go to Marshall Field.
-The department went to work--
-Police department, thank
you for your pledge.
-Every police
squad in the city--
-Police department, thank you!
-Would be able specific area.
Every entrance and exit to the
Los Angeles city sewer system
of 700 miles.
-APB-- big sale at Winchell's.
-Joel--
-Stop!
-Squads headed for the entrance
where, according to the map,
Butcher had hidden the money.
Our job was to stop him.
And that made me think
of one specific question.
-Who built Stonehenge?
-When we found him, could
this monster be stopped?
I, for one, wasn't sure.
-Huh, guess I'll climb
into this Metallica video.
Huh, huh.
-We can crash in my Nash.
-Cruising for burgers.
-Haha, it looks like
they're both standing.
-They are.
-I think he's
somewhere around here!
-Nice baby moves.
-Mhm, thank you.
-The engineers mapped
out each possible exit.
-No, the car.
-A squad of officers are
spotted at every point.
The Butcher can be caught--
[GROWLING]
[IMITATE GROWLING AND BARKING]
-Scanners.
-A flame thrower might stop him.
-Flame thrower.
-Oh, he's crying.
Honey.
-See we have one with us here.
-Have you thought about what'll
happen if this doesn't work?
-Come on, hit him.
You know you want to.
-No.
I've been praying too
hard that it will work.
-Mickey Rooney's summer
place is searched.
-Ghostbusters.
-(FRENCH ACCENT) And so
Philippe and the police
crawl into the sewer and--
-Hey, quit pushing back there.
Ooh, ooh.
-Norton?
-Hey, yeah, Ralphie boy?
-Um, Ted, I can
see up your pants.
-Oh!
-Ah, there.
-Yuck, don't even ask!
-You know, think
of all the burritos
they sell in this town.
[SOUNDS OF DISGUST]
-(SINGING) Randy Rooter, roller
scooter, down the city sewer.
-The tunnel.
-You know, nobody
needs to hide this bad.
-Hm-mm.
-[SNIFFS] Oh!
-Yuck.
-[COUGHS]
-Oh, he sat in it!
Oh!
Oh, god, he jumped in it!
-[SPUTTERS_AND_SPITS]
-Kinda looks like
the dog from Pogo.
-Where's the men's room?
-You're soaking in it.
[LAUGHTER]
-We kid, of course.
-Over here, boys, I
got the poop on him.
-(SINGING) I'm
singing in the filth.
Just singing--
-It's a gang of Sunday
night mystery movies!
-Oh, stop it, just stop it.
-Anything you say,
Mr. Doughnut Joke.
-Oooh.
-Sure wish I had some shoes on.
-I'm Dickens.
He's Fenster.
We're cops.
-This is where we split up.
-I'll go straight ahead.
-I'll go with the
guy with the bazooka.
-Hey, take a look, Chief.
It's a boogie board.
-Right over there, now.
-They're in Karen
Finley's wet bar.
-Ooohh.
-Oh, look what it says
on the wall there.
If it's yellow, let it mellow.
If it's brown, flush it down.
-Oh.
-Hey, found half a doughnut.
Who wants it?
-[SPUTTERS] Not a sewer
doughnut joke, no.
-Well, he's the
life of the party.
-Minutes?
-Guy's gonna use
fire, and there's
all that methane down there.
-You know, this is
kind of like a Close
Encounters of the "Turd" Kind.
-Ohhh.
-Sorry.
-By the smell of this, I
guess we're under Barstow.
-Oh, I lost the sensor.
-No, you didn't.
-Now look, there's a perfectly
good cabbage over there.
-Hmm, must have taken a
wrong turn at Albuquerque.
-If that's right,
we're off our course.
We'll have to back-track.
-(SNIFFING) Back draft?
[THEME MUSIC]
-[CHUCKLES_STUPIDLY] Pretty.
-Come into the light,
Indestructible man!
-Oh, I think I just found the
legendary goldfish graveyard.
-Hey, a wheat penny!
-Oh, it's the treasure
of the sewer madre.
-This film was
originally in Odorama.
-I believe it.
-Huh?
-Baseball cards!
-This way.
OK, now this way.
-Hey, it stinks, but it's
still better than an SNL.
-I'll say.
-Hey, wait up, you guys!
-Let's sneak up on
him real loudly.
-It's getting gritty.
-Hold it, Butcher!
-Let him have it.
-Oh, they're hitting
him with chili peppers!
-He burned his gut, you see.
-I am indestructible,
but really stung.
[BACKGROUND MUSIC SWELLS]
-"I Love Lucy."
-OK, for all practical purposes,
almost indestructible man.
-Think of the doughnuts I
could buy with this loot.
-You wanna hit him, or shall I?
-Aw, you do it.
-I can't.
-I can't either.
-I wonder who the
stool pigeon was.
-Oohh.
-It was a black and tarry night.
-Ooh, light a
match, you're right.
-This is like the
end of "Cape Fear."
-Now that put me off my dinner.
-You know, I'd rather light
a single indestructible man
than curse the darkness.
-Oohh.
-I think he's
incontinent man now.
-Oooh.
-Dum, dum, dum, da- whoa!
-Ew.
-(LISPING) I'm the scariest
clown in the circus.
Brrrr.
-Electric monkey bars.
Great idea.
-Actually, now,
I think he's just
the Incredibly Resilient Man.
-Not To Be Trifled With Man.
-Takes A Licking And
Keeps On Ticking Man.
-Harry Connick!
-Where?
Oh.
-Oh, hey, how about that?
-Now, you guys should
have gone while we
were down in the sewer.
-[MOCK_CRIES] I just
gotta keep telling
myself I'm indestructible.
I'm indestructible!
-Would you come here, please?
Gadding about like
a crazy person.
-You know, this is
kinda like Macbeth,
only it's not good at all.
-Yeah.
Too long, hard to watch.
Bad luck for the
performers who act in it.
-Yep, yep.
-It's all ruined now.
I was indestructible,
and now look.
-I squandered my
indestructibility.
Let this be a lesson.
Be courteous to those who
are not indestructible.
Thank you.
-Uh, yeah, you got a
bit of it on your, uh--
-Ew.
-This is gonna end with
a big speech about, um--
-No, no, I think he's gonna
go to the woman, and, uh,
he's gonna--
-No, no, I think
it's about the bomb.
-Oh.
-Well, that'd
figure, wouldn't it?
-[SNIFFS] Yes, he's
around here somewhere.
-Hey, Mom's out there,
and if she sees us,
she'll make us come in.
-Mr. Wallenda!
Don't let your family
attempt the pyramid!
-Ss-- sanctuary!
Sanctuary!
-Hope it's a shower.
-(SINGING) Choo Choo
Charlie was an engineer.
-Sir, you're not union.
Please.
-The giant gantry now moves
away from the Gemini Capsule
and its titan.
-Vertigo.
-He hijacked a crane.
-I think he's improvising now.
He's completely off-script.
-Hey, it's the world
famous Duluth Lift Bridge.
-When in Duluth--
-Darn fool indestructible kid!
-I'm glad I belong
to this gym, but I
don't know how to
work the machines.
-Oh, he's gonna do that
Krazy Glue demonstration.
That's what it is.
-Gumby, get off the tower.
-(FALSETTO) Top of
the world, Pokey!
-Ladies and
gentlemen, it's Liza!
-Well you know, maybe he
wasn't the title character.
Maybe somebody else is
the Indestructible Man.
-Ugh.
-[SNIFFS] Ew!
-Yuck.
-Smells worse than the sewer.
-I'll say.
-So.
-And the tremendous
shock of electricity
that brought the Butcher
back to life was destroyed.
-Uh, buddy.
Camera's over here.
[WHISTLES] Yoo-hoo!
-$600,000 stolen in
the armored truck
robbery has been recovered.
Case closed.
-So, you got the
book rights, huh?
-Well, here are the slightest
comments for your record.
-Sinus comment?
-I had to fill in a few spots
with my own guesses, but--
-I think it's pretty funny.
-That's about the size of it.
-Did you get any sleep?
-Oh, some.
Not much.
-How's the girl today?
-Well, I called the
hospital about an hour ago.
She'd gone.
-Gone?
Where?
-She told them she
was a working girl,
and that she'd been away from
the job too long already.
-Ooh.
I get it.
-Quite a girl.
-Say no more.
-Yeah.
-Say, uh, how about that
time off I've got coming?
-48 hours, beginning right now.
Get some rest.
-Yay!
-Hey, it's the end!
-It's over!
-We can go now!
Yay!
It's over!
-Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Know
-Aww.
-Epilogue.
-Epi-lady.
-Epicenter.
-Ipecac.
-The past 72 hours
seem like a bad dream.
That rest in the
hospital today really
gave me a new lease on life.
-And the Jell-O was delicious.
-Now that it's over--
-Wind it up!
-Can't believe it
actually happened.
-Please
-The important thing is to
remember it is all over.
-(IN UNISON) Thank God!
-I suppose you'll be
assigned to another case,
and I'll have to give up
hamburgers in the front seat
of the car for--
-Yes, they have me assigned
to the Illustrated Man now.
-I've thought about that.
-And stopped.
-In fact, I decided to
do something about it.
-I started by talking the
Captain into a short holiday.
And, uh, just about an
hour ago, I got you fired.
-What?
-Arf?
-What did you do that for?
-Did you say arf?
-I figured that being my wife
would take up all of your time.
-Oh, please.
He should quit his job.
Strippers make a lot
more money, you know.
-Even if I wanted
to say, I couldn't.
-Yes, you can.
Rethink.
-Please.
-You're not supposed to
say no to a detective.
-Let's get out of here.
-Can I tuck about a dollar
in your G-string? [CHUCKLES]
-[GROANS]
[DOORS CLOSING]
-Come on, Skippy.
Read it, sign it,
get on with it.
-Well, what is it?
-It's an official affidavit
stating that you will never
again darken our portals with
crummy cop doughnut jokes.
-Well, it's not an
affidavit per se, Crow.
It's more of a contractual
mandamus against a specific
actus reus in which the off-
-Servo.
-Huh?
-Shut up.
-Sorry.
-Listen, you guys.
I promise I won't do any
more cop and doughnut jokes,
but I'm not gonna sign
this silly piece of paper.
-Oh, really, Joel, it's for your
own protection as well as ours.
-OK, well, uh, you guys
got to sign it too.
-All right, fair enough.
Now read it aloud.
-OK, uh.
Uh, "I, state your name."
-(IN UNISON) "I,
state your name."
-Oh, you guys, now cut it out!
That's just as bad as
doing doughnut jokes!
-Sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-It's my fault.
-OK.
I'll read it by myself, then.
"Whereas I hereby warrant that
I will cease and desist
all jokes, quips,
humorous anecdotes, bon mots,
and other devices of repartee
pertaining to, exclusively
and in general,
all references and observations,
direct or indirect,
pertaining to, but
not exclusively,
in description of law
enforcement officials who
ingest, solicit, consume, or
hoard those pastries which can
be described under the
terms of the "code-i-cile"--
-Codicil.
-"Codicil below as belonging
to a nonspecific group,
except in the common
parlance, as doughnuts
and doughnut-related pastries
heretofore known as doughnuts."
-Uh, there's an exemption
for FBI agents and muffins
in the codicil.
-Yeah, we thought we
could be flexible on that.
But keep going.
-"This being enacted on this day
and enforced in "perpetu-ity"--
-Perpetuity.
-"Perpetuity throughout
the universe,
we hereunto set our hand
and seal on the day above
mentioned--" OK, I guess
I can live with that.
-OK.
-All right, good.
-All right.
-I'll have Gypsy
notarize this later.
-Gypsy's a notary?
-Mhm.
Stamp it, please.
OK.
You know, the little
friends are right, folks.
Let's put an end to
the hackneyed practice
of cop and doughnut jokes.
Thank you, won't you?
What do you think, sirs?
-Boy, isn't that the truth.
You know, boys, I don't
even like doughnuts.
I'm not saying I won't
eat them if they're there.
-Hey, tell them about
the Chinese food.
-That's right.
Today we had Chinese food.
-Moo goo gai pan,
and it was terrific.
And, you know, we're
not all Irish, either.
-Well, Kevin here is
Irish, but me, I'm Danish.
-[LAUGHS_LOUDLY]
-I don't like you.
-Hey, cool, man.
And you know the thing
about the flat feet?
I got arches the size
of the monkey house
at the Brookfield Zoo.
And I've got this bunion.
Have you seen the size of this
sucker on the side of my--
-Thanks for sharing, guys.
Can we help you?
-Uh, yes sir, as a matter
of fact, you can, um.
You can show a little
respect for your neighbors
by keeping the music
down, and, uh, next time,
you'll avoid a citation.
Just sign right
there on the bottom.
-It's these rock walls.
The sound goes
right through them.
You know, if I had my way,
I'd outlaw these sub-woofers.
-That's right.
Hey, do us all a
favor next time,
and think of others first.
Will ya?
OK?
Have a good day.
-Oh, uh, thank you, uh--
-Until next time, Joel.
Push the button, Frank.
-Can I see your gun?
-(WARNING) Frank!
[CHUCKLES]
-By the way, was that
your car out front?
[THEME MUSIC]